Guide to the Vanguard Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Editorial Files
  - Grattus, Jack (Box 56)
  - Greer, Genevieve (Box 56)
  - Gregg, Charles (Box 56)
  - Gregory, Blanche (Box 57)
  - Gregory, Horace (Box 57)
  - Griffith, Paul (Box 57)
  - Grigson, Geoffrey (Box 57)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni (Box 57)
  - Groth, John (Box 57)
  - Groth, Kimball & Feuchtwanger (Box 57)
  - Gruber, Ruth (Michaels) (Box 58)
  - Gruening, Ernest (Box 58)
  - Guck, Dorothy (Box 58)
  - Guerney, Bernard (Box 58)
  - Gummere, John F. (Box 58)
  - Hagen, Harry W. (Box 59)
  - Haldane, Charlotte (Box 59)
  - Hallen, Ingrid (Box 59)
  - Hamburger, Estelle (Box 59)
  - Hamilton, H.E. (Box 59)
  - Hamlin, C.H. (Box 59)
  - Hammond & Hammond (Box 59)
  - Hankin, Cliff (Box 59)
  - Hanna, Mark (Box 59)
  - Hannum, Alberta (Box 59)
  - Hansen, Zora (Box 59)
  - Hanser (Box 59)
  - Harcourt Brace (Box 60)
  - Harris, Reed (Box 60)
  - Harrison, Hal (Box 60)
  - Hart, Ernest (Box 60)
  - Hart, Marion (Box 60)
  - Harvill Press (Box 60)
  - Haskins, Ilma (Box 60)
  - Hauswirth, Frieda (Box 60)
  - Hawthorne, Nathaniel (Box 61)
  - Heald, Weldon F. (Box 61)
  - Heard, H.F. (Box 61)
  - Hearne, John (Box 61)
  - Hecker (Box 61)
  - Hector, Shirley (Box 61)
  - Heimler, Eugene (Box 61)
  - Helbrant, Maurice (Box 61)
  - Held, John (Box 61)
  - Heller, Annie (Box 61)
  - Helweg, Hans (Box 61)
  - Henle, Guy (Box 62)
  - Henle, James (Box 62)
  - Henle, Jane (Box 62)
  - Henle, Mary (Box 62)
  - Henle, Peter (Box 62)
  - Henle, Theda (Box 62)
  - Henry, John M. (Box 63 & 64)
  - Herald, George (Box 65)
  - Herlen Literary Agency (Box 65)
  - Herman, Fred (Box 65)
  - Hess, Myra (Box 65)
  - Heyen, William (Box 65)
  - Higbee Company (Box 65)
  - Hill, Earle (Box 66)
  - Hill, Marie (Box 66)
  - Hillman, Howard (Box 66)
  - Hinde, Thomas (Box 66)
  - Hines, James (Box 66)
  - Hirschmann, Ira (Box 66)
  - Hodann, Max (Box 67)
  - Hogeboom, Amy (Box 67)
  - Holland, Janice (Box 67)
  - Hollis & Cater Ltd. (Box 67)
  - Holmes & Silverman (Box 67)
  - Holmes, Marshall (Box 67)
  - Hooten, Barbara (Box 67)
  - Hopkins, Hugh (Box 67)
  - Horch, Franz (Box 67)
  - Horizon magazine (Box 68)
  - Horizon-American Corp (Box 68)
  - Houghton, Mifflin (Box 68)
  - Howe, DeWolfe (Box 68)
  - Huber, Hogge & Sons (Box 68)
  - Hull, George H. (Box 68)
  - Humphries, Robert (Box 68)
  - Hunter, Edward (Box 68)
  - Hunter, Edward (Box 69)
  - H.R. Huntting Company (Box 70)
  - Hupka, Robert (Box 70)
  - Hurling, Joan (Box 70)
  - Hutchinson, H.S. (Box 70)
  - Hurley & Suschitzky (Box 70)
  - Huyghe, Rene (Box 70)
  - Ickes, Harold (Box 71)
  - Ilsley, Velma (Box 71)
  - Inactive Authors (Box 71)
  - Ingersoll & Brennan (Box 71)
  - Institute Publishing Co. (Box 71)
  - International Literary Management (Box 72)
  - Isdaacs, Susan (Box 72)
  - J.M. Dent & Sons Ltd (Box 72)
  - Jackets designs, etc. (Box 72)
  - Jackinson, Alex (Box 72)
  - Jackson, Geoffrey (Box 72)
  - Jacques Chambrun Inc (Box 72)
  - Jaffe, Herb (Box 72)
  - Jagendorf, M.A. (Box 73-74)
  - Jagendorf, M.A. (Box 75)
  - James Brown Assoc. (Box 75)
  - James, E.O. (Box 75)
  - Jay, Frank (Box 76)
  - Jenkyns, Chris (Box 76)
  - Jessup, Ronald (Box 76)
  - Johnson, Eyvind (Box 76)
  - Jolas, Eugene (Box 76)
  - Jones, Cynon Beaton (Box 76)
  - Jones, Francis A. (Box 76)
  - Jones, Helen H. (Box 76)
  - Jones, Idwal (Box 76)
  - Jordan, Philip (Box 76)
  - Joseph, Nannine (Box 77)
  - Junior Literary Guild (Box 77)
  - Kafka, Franz (Box 77)
  - Kagen, Genevieve (Box 77)
  - Kahn, Harry J. (Box 77)
  - Kahn, Sholom J. (Box 77)
  - Kallet & Schlink (Box 77)
  - Kallet, Arthur (Box 77)
  - Kamm, Josephine (Box 77)
  - Karp, David (Box 77)
  - Karp, Lila (Box 77)
  - Kasdan, Sara (Box 78)
  - Katz, Moselle (Box 79)
  - Kauffman, Henry (Box 79)
  - Kedron, Nora (Box 79)
  - Kehoe, Monica (Box 79)
  - Kehrlein, Oliver (Box 79)
  - Keith, Ralph W. (Box 79)
  - Kemmer, Rick (Box 79)
  - Kendrigan, G.M. (Box 79)
  - Kennedy, Mary (Box 79)
  - Kenton, Edna (Box 79)
  - Kepner, Charles D. (Box 79)
  - Kerenyi, Karl (Box 79)
  - Kimball, Yeffe (Box 79)
  - King Features Syn. (Box 80)
  - Kirtland, Elizabeth (Box 80)
  - Klarsfeld, Beate (Box 80)
  - Klausner, Bertha (Box 81)
  - Kleinsinger, G & Kapp, Paul (Box 81)
  - Kling, Samuel (Box 82)
  - Knight, Hilary (Box 82)
  - Knopf, Alfred (Box 82)
  - Koeppen, Wolfgang (Box 82)
  - Krleza, Miroslav (Box 82)
  - Kropotkin, Peter & Stirner, Max (Box 82)
  - Krumgold, Joseph (Box 82)
  - Kuhn, Ferninand (Box 83)
  - Kupfer, J.M. (Box 83)
  - Labin, Susanne (Box 83)
  - Ladies Home Journal (Box 83)
  - Laine, Pascal (Box 83)
  - Lainez, Manuel M. (Box 83)
  - Lambert & Feasley (Box 84)
  - Lambert, Alice Elinor (Box 84)
  - Lambert Wilson Literary Agt. (Box 84)
  - Landers Agency Inc. (Box 84)
  - Langner, Nola (Box 84)
  - Lannog, Richard (Box 84)
  - La Page International (Box 84)
  - Laronsse de la Musique (Box 84)
  - Larrabee, Harold (Box 84)
  - Larson, Cecilia (Box 84)
  - Larson, Gosta (Box 84)
  - Lassimonne, Denise (Box 84)
  - Lavine, Emmanuel (Box 84)
  - Laurence Pollinger Ltd (Box 84)
  - Laurence Pollinger Ltd. (Box 85)
  - Laurie, T. Werner (Box 85)
  - Lawrence & Lee (Box 85)
  - Lawrence & Wishart (Box 85)
  - Lawrence, D.H. (Box 85)
  - Lawrence, Jerome (Box 85)
  - Lawrence, John (Box 85)
  - Lawton, George (Box 86)
  - Leader, Pauline (Box 86)
  - Leao, Sylvia (Box 86)
  - LeBayou, Alice (Box 86)
  - Lee, John A (Box 86)
  - Leekley, Thomas B. (Box 86)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. (Box 86)
  - Leight, Edward (Box 87)
  - Leighton, Frances Spatz (Box 87)
  - L'Engle, Madeline (Box 87)
  - Lenormand, H.R. (Box 87)
  - Lenski, Branko (Box 87)
  - Lenski, Branko (Box 88)
  - Leonard, Phyllis (Box 88)
  - LeSourd, M. (Box 88)
  - LeSourd, Paul (Box 88)
  - Lester & Orpen (Box 88)
  - Lethbridge, T.C. (Box 88)
  - Levoy, Myron (Box 88)
  - Lewi, Grant (Box 88)
  - Lewis (Box 88)
  - Lewis, Arthur (Box 88)
  - Lewis, Maynah (Box 88)
  - Lewis, W.M. (Mrs) (Box 88)
  - Lewton, Val (Box 89)
  - Licciardi, Emily (Box 89)
  - Lieber, Leslie & Toni Miller (Box 89)
  - Lief, Alfred (Box 89)
  - Life Magazine (Box 89)
  - Links, J.G. (Box 89)
  - Linna, Vaino (Box 89)
  - Lion Books (Box 89)
  - List of Author Correspondence in Storage at Duham & Reid (Box 89)
  - Literary Features Ltd. (Box 89)
  - Literary Guild (Box 89)
  - Littauer & Wilkenson (Box 89)
  - Litvinoff, Emanuel (Box 89)
  - Lloyd, Robin (Box 90)
  - Lobsenz, Amelia (Box 90)
  - Lobsenz & Company (Box 90)
  - Locke, Edith Raymond (Box 90)
  - Lord, Isabel (Box 90)
  - Lourie, Richard (Box 90)
  - Loveland, Constance (Box 90)
  - Low, Mary (Box 91)
  - Lowenfels, Walter (Box 91)
  - Lowery, Bruce (Box 91)
  - Lubis, Mochtar (Box 91)
  - Lucas, Christopher (Box 91)
  - Lundberg, Ferdinand (Box 91)
  - Lutyens, Mary (Box 91)
  - Lyons, John Henry (Box 91)
  - Mass, Dorothy (Box 92)
  - McCall Corporation (Box 92)
  - McCall, Monica (Box 92)
  - McCallum, Neil (Box 92)
  - McClellan, J.L. (Mrs) (Box 92)
  - McClintock, Inez (Box 92)
  - McClintock, Marshall (Box 92)
  - McClintock, Theodore (Box 92)
  - McCrindle, J.F. (Box 92)
  - McCullough, David (Box 92)
  - MacDonald & Company (Box 92)
  - MCDonald, Dwight (Box 92)
  - McDowell, Edwin (Box 92)
  - McGinnis, Bruce (Box 92)
  - McGrath, Fern (Box 93)
  - McGrath, Tom (Box 93)
  - McGuire, Nellie (Box 93)
  - McInerny, Ralph (Box 93)
  - McIntosh & Otis (Box 93)
  - McIntosh, E. (Box 93)
  - McKay, Margaret (Box 93)
  - McKean, Elly (Box 93)
  - McKean, Lloyd (Box 93)
  - McKee & Mouche (Box 93)
  - Mackenzie, Norman (Box 93)
  - McKinley, Silas (Box 94)
  - McKone, Jim (Box 95 & 96)
  - McKone, Jim (Box 97)
  - McKown, Robin (Box 97)
  - McLuhan, Marshall (Box 98)
  - McMahon, Francis (Box 98)
  - McNamara, Edward (Box 99)
  - McQueen, Noel (Box 99)
  - Madden, E.S (Box 99)
  - Maiden, Cecil (Box 99)
  - Malone, Catherine F. (Harvard library) (Box 99)
  - Malvern, Gladys (Box 99)
  - Manhattan Literary Agency (Box 99)
  - Manley, Robert (Box 99)
  - Manley, Seon (Box 99)
  - Manley, Seon (Box 100)
  - Manning, Elizabeth (Box 101)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust (Box 101)
  - Marcotte, Gilles (Box 101)
  - Marion, John (Box 101)
  - Marion, John (Box 102)
  - Markova, Alicia (Box 102)
  - Marsh, Fred (Box 102)
  - Marsh, Margaret (Box 102)
  - Marston, Mardell (Box 102)
  - Martin, Arthur (Box 102)
  - Martin, Ben (Box 102)
  - Martin, Peg (Box 102)
  - Martinetti, Ronald (Box 102)
  - Marty, Sid (Box 102)
  - Marvin, Linda (Box 102)
  - Mass Observation (Box 102)
  - Matthews, Clyde (Box 102)
  - Max Pfeffer (Box 102)
  - Max Reinhardt Ltd. (Box 102)
  - Maxey, Dale (Box 102)
  - Mayes, Herbert (Box 102)
  - Mayfield, Julian (Box 103)
  - Mazzocco, Edward (Box 103)
  - Melcher, Marguerite (Box 103)
  - Mercal (Box 103)
  - Methodist Pub. House (Box 103)
  - Meyer, Edith Patterson (Box 104)
  - Meyer, Helmut (Box 104)
  - Michael, Maurice (Box 104)
  - Middleton, Beverly (Box 104)
  - Mikol, Vera (Box 104)
  - Miller, Jane & Givens, Mona (Box 104)
  - Miller, Toni (Box 104)
  - Milton, George Fort (Box 104)
  - Mitchell, Edwin (Box 104)
  - Mitchison, Naomi (Box 104)
  - Molarsky, Del (Box 104)
  - Molnar, Terene (Box 104)
  - Molyneaux, Thomas W. (Box 104)
  - Monelli, Paolo (Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous lists, correspondence, bills, invoices, advertisements, etc. (Box 104A)
  - Montgomery, Charlotte (Box 105)
  - Moore, Nancy (Box 106)
  - Morgan, Henry (Box 106)
  - Morrison, N.B. (Box 106)
  - Mozart, W.A. (Box 106)
  - Muller, Herman (Box 106)
  - Murphy, James (Box 107)
  - Murray, A.A. (Box 108)
  - Murray, William (Box 108)
  - Museum Press (Box 108)
  - Myers, Paul (Box 108)
  - Naipaul, V.S. (Box 109)
  - Namioka, Lensy (Box 109)
  - Nannine, Joseph (Box 109)
  - Nation, Terry (Box 109)
  - National Rural Electric Coop Ass. (Box 109)
  - Neal, Harry (Box 109)
  - Neuberger & Kahn (Box 109)
  - Neuberger, Elsa (Box 109)
  - Neuberger, Richard (Box 109)
  - New American Library of World Literature (Box 110)
  - New York Lithographing Co. (Box 123 110)
  - New York Public Library (Box 123 110)
  - Neyhart, Louise (Box 123 110)
  - Nieri, Lorraine (Box 123 110)
  - Nixon, Edna (Box 123 110)
  - Noakes, David (Box 123 110)
  - Noel-Baker, Francis (Box 123 110)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol 1964-1974 (Box 111)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol 1975 (Box 112)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol 1976-1979 (Box 113)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol (Box 114 & 115)
  - Oates, Joycer Carol Manuscripts: "The Assassins" & "Poisoned Kiss" (Box 116)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Galley Proofs: C - D (Box 117)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Galley Proofs: D - E (Box 118)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Galley Proofs: G - M (Box 119)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Galley Proofs: M - U (Box 120)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Galley Proofs (photocpies) (Box 121)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol Printed Materials (Box 122)
  - O'Brien, Bill T. (Box 123)
  - O'Donnell, James J.O. (Box 123)
  - Oglanby, Elva (Box 123)
  - O'Hair, Madalyn (Box 123)
  - Okudzhava, Bulat (Box 123)
  - Olds, Lee (Box 123)
  - Oliver, Daniel (Box 123)
  - O'Mara, Patrick (Box 123)
  - Ostrander, Gilman (Box 123)
  - Pageant Press, Inc. (Box 124)
  - Pallottino & Hurlimann (Box 124)
  - Palmer, Bissell (Box 124)
  - Palmer, Rachel Lynn (Box 124)
  - Pape, Lee (Box 124)
  - Parents Magazine (Box 124)
  - Parrish, Max & Co. Ltd. (Box 124)
  - Parry, Albert (Box 124)
  - Parry, Albert (Box 125)
  - Parsons, Cynthia (Box 125)
  - Parton, Margaret (Box 125)
  - Patai, Raphael (Box 125)
  - Paterson, Mark (Box 125)
  - Patten, Bernard M. (Box 125)
  - Payne, Robert (Box 125)
  - Peare, Catherine (Box 125)
  - Pearn, Pollinger & Higham (Box 126)
  - Pearn, Pollinger & Higham (Box 127)
  - Pease, Josephine (Box 127)
  - Peattie, Donald (Box 128)
  - Peattie, Roderick (Box 128)
  - Peattie, Roderick (Box 129-131)
  - Pederson-Krag, Geraldine (Box 132)
  - Peic - Peli (Box 132)
  - Peller, Lili (Box 132)
  - Pepper, Morton (Box 133-136)
  - Perkins, Virginia Chase (Box 137)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton (Box 137)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton (Box 138)
  - Perry, William E. (Box 138)
  - Petruzzi, Eleanor (Box 138)
  - Phillips, Leslie Gordon (Box 138)
  - Phillips, Robert (Box 138)
  - Phillips, Robert (Box 139)
  - Phillipson, Morris (Box 139)
  - Pidoll, Carl (Box 140)
  - Pinkas (Box 140)
  - Plante, David (Box 140)
  - Plates for books (Box 140)
  - Plattner, Felix Alfred (Box 140)
  - Pocket Books Inc (Box 140)
  - Pohl, Frederick (Box 140)
  - Poliakor, Leon (Box 140)
  - Popular Library (Box 141)
  - Porcelain, Sidney E. (Box 142)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne (Box 142)
  - Postgate, Raymond (Box 142)
  - Powel, Harford (Box 142)
  - Powledge, Fred (Box 142)
  - Practical Science Publishing Co. (Box 142)
  - Preminger, Jaffe, Stuart Agency (Box 142)
  - Preminger, Otto (Box 142)
  - Preti, Luigi (Box 142)
  - Pringle, Henry (Box 142)
  - Prior, Ann (Box 142)
  - Promotion and publicity releases (Box 143)
  - Protter, Eric (Box 144)
  - Publishers' Weekly (Box 144)
  - Pulitzer Prizes (Box 144)
  - Purcell, John (Box 144)
  - Pym, Barbara (Box 144)
  - Pyramid Books (Box 144)
  - Quick Magazine (Box 145)
  - Quinn, Andrea (Box 145)
  - Rabe, Peter (Box 145)
  - Raftery, Gerald (Box 145)
  - Raimondi, Emily (Box 145)
  - Randolph, Vance (Box 145)
  - Random House (Box 145)
  - Read, Grantly D. (Box 145)
  - Reimann Guenter (Box 145)
  - Reingold, Lester (Box 145)
  - Reitman, Ben (Box 145)
  - Reitman, Dorothy (Box 145)
  - Remainder Book Co. (Box 145)
  - Repass, Richard (Box 145)
  - Reports on "Japanese Stories" (Box 146)
  - Reprint Interest & Ideas (Box 146)
  - Revusky, Abraham (Box 146)
  - Rhylick, Frank (Box 146)
  - Richards, Bernard G. (Box 146)
  - Richardson, Joanna (Box 146)
  - Rinehart & Co., Inc. (Box 146)
  - Roberts, David (Box 146)
  - Robinson, Lura (Box 146)
  - Rockefeller, John W. (Box 146)
  - Rockefeller, J.W. (Box 147)
  - Rohde, Peggy Ann (Box 147)
  - Ronald, George (Box 147)
  - Ronne, Finn (Box 147)
  - Rooney, Frank (Box 147)
  - Rosenberg, Elliot (Box 147)
  - Ross, George (Box 147)
  - Row, Peterson & Co. (Box 147)
  - Rubin, Estelle (Box 147)
  - Rubinstein, Nash & Co. (Box 147)
  - Rudolph, Marguerita (Box 147)
  - Russell, Robert (Box 147)
  - Russell, Robert (Box 148)
  - Rutherford, Peggy (Box 148)
  - Sager, Gordon (Box 149)
  - St. Clair, William (Box 149)
  - St. John, Joseph (Box 149)
  - Saint-Marcoux (Box 149)
  - Salter, Stefan (Box 149)
  - Samivel & Audrain (Box 149)
  - Sandblom, Paul (Box 149)
  - Sansom, William (Box 149)
  - Saturday Review (Box 150)
  - Saunders, Marion (Box 150)
  - Saxby, Joyce (Box 150)
  - Schaffner, John (Box 151)
  - Schelling, Ernest (Box 151)
  - Schenk De Regniers (Box 151)
  - Schloming, Gordon (Box 151)
  - Schlosser, Alexander (Box 151)
  - Schmidgall, Benny (Box 151)
  - Schmidt, Michael (Box 151)
  - Schneider, Benjamin (Box 151)
  - Schnitman, L. Seth (Box 151)
  - Scholastic Magazine (Box 151)
  - Schultz, Pearle Henriksen (Box 151)
  - Schultz, Pearle H. (Box 152)
  - Schurr, Cathleen & Maas, Dorothy (Box 152)
  - Schuyter, Vera (Box 152)
  - Scott, Foresman & Co. (Box 152)
  - Scribner's (Box 152)
  - Script Service Del. (Box 152)
  - Searle, Ronald (Box 153)
  - Seay, Wilson L. (Box 153)
  - Secker & Warburg (Box 153)
  - Secret Societies (Box 153)
  - Self, Margaret C. (Box 153)
  - Sender, Ramon (Box 153)
  - Sender, Toni (Box 153)
  - Seth-Smith, E.K. (Box 153)
  - Shadid, Michael (Box 153)
  - Shafer, Burr (Box 153)
  - Shafer, Burr (Box 154)
  - Shafer, Evelyne (Box 154)
  - Shamir, Moshe (Box 154)
  - Shannon, Liz (Box 154)
  - Shannon, William (Box 154)
  - Sharp, Arthur (Box 154)
  - Shaw, Bernard (Box 154)
  - Sherpa Adventures (Box 155)
  - Shiel, M.P. (Box 155)
  - Shippey, Lee (Box 156)
  - Shrifte, Estelle (Teddy) (Box 156)
  - Shrifte, Evelyn (Box 156)
  - Shrifte, Herbert (Box 156)
  - Shrifte, Herbert (Box 157-159)
  - Sidgwick & Jackson Ltd (Box 160)
  - Siegmund, Warren (Box 160)
  - Simon, Henry (Box 160)
  - Simon, Hilda (Box 160)
  - Simpson, William (Box 161)
  - Sims, Dorothy R. (Box 161)
  - Sinclair, Upton (Box 161)
  - Singer, Israel Joshua (Box 161)
  - Singer, Joe (Box 161)
  - Singer, June (Box 161)
  - Sissman, L.E. (Box 161)
  - Sitwell, Edith (Box 162)
  - Sitwell, Edith (Box 163)
  - Skolsky (Box 163)
  - Slade, Caroline (Box 164-165)
  - Slade, Caroline (Box 166)
  - Slay, Bill & Jane (Box 166)
  - Slobodkin, Florence (Box 166)
  - Slobodkin, Louis (Box 166)
  - Slobodkin, Louis (Box 167)
  - Slobodkin, Louis (Box 168)
  - Small, David H. (Box 168)
  - Smedley, Agnes (Box 168)
  - Smirnow, Louis (Box 168)
  - Smith, Constance (Box 168)
  - Smith, H. Allen (Box 168)
  - Smith, Marjorie E. (Box 168)
  - Smith, Ruth (Box 168)
  - Smith, Sara (Box 168)
  - Smoli (Box 168)
  - Snyder, Henry (Box 168)
  - Society of Authors (Box 169)
  - Soothill, Henry (Box 169)
  - Sootin, Harry (Box 169)
  - Spanier, Muriel (Box 169)
  - Spaulding, Amy E. (Box 169)
  - Spender, Stephen (Box 169)
  - Spivack, Robert (Box 169)
  - Spodheim, Renee (Box 169)
  - Stagg, Jerry (Box 169)
  - Stallworth, Anne (Box 169)
  - Standard, Stella & Paul (Box 169)
  - Stanev, Emilian (Box 170)
  - Stanley, R. & Neame, A. (Box 170)
  - Staples Press (Box 170)
  - Steinberg, Barbara (Box 170)
  - Steiner, Charlotte (Box 170)
  - Stern & Reubens (Box 170)
  - Stern & Reubens (Box 171)
  - Sters, Virginia (Box 171)
  - Stevens, E. V. (Box 171)
  - Stone, Clifford (Box 171)
  - Stout, Rex (Box 171)
  - Strassman, Toni (Box 171)
  - Strassora, Helena (Box 171)
  - Streeter, Edward (Box 171)
  - Strom, Elsie (Box 171)
  - Strousse, Flora (Box 171)
  - Sturdy, John Rhodes (Box 171)
  - Styles. Showell (Box 171)
  - Supreme Ad Service (Box 171)
  - Swabacker, Leslie (Box 171)
  - Sweezey, Francis (Box 171)
  - Taber, Grace (Box 172)
  - Tabori, Paul (Box 172)
  - Taktsis, Coctas (Box 172)
  - Tanner, Patrick (Box 172)
  - Tanners, Ann (Box 172)
  - Targ, William (Box 173)
  - Taplinger, Dick (Box 173)
  - Taylor (Box 173)
  - Taylor, Alice (Box 173)
  - Taylor, G. Rattray (Box 173)
  - Taylor, William S. (Box 173)
  - Terrett, Courtney (Box 173)
  - Teuffen, Dietrich (Box 173)
  - Thaler, Susan (Box 173)
  - Thames & Hudson Ltd. (Box 173)
  - Thapur, Raj (Box 173)
  - Theroux, Paul (Box 173)
  - Thomashefsky, Harry (Box 174)
  - Thompson, Francis (Box 174)
  - Tillhagen, C.H. (Box 174)
  - Titus, Evelyn (Box 174)
  - Tobias, Doris (Box 174)
  - Toksvig, Signe (Box 174)
  - Tomb, Dianne Licky (Box 174)
  - Tomei, Stelio (Box 174)
  - Torrey, Arthur (Box 174)
  - Toscanini, Antek (Box 174)
  - Tracey, Don (Box 175)
  - Trease, Geoffrey (Box 175)
  - Trilling, Lionel (Box 176)
  - Trip, Paul (Box 176)
  - Troyer, Johannes (Box 176)
  - Truman, Harry (Box 176)
  - Tsao, Alex (Box 176)
  - Turlington, Catherine (Box 176)
  - Turpin, J.B. (Box 176)
  - Tyler, Parker (Box 176)
  - Ullman, George (Box 177)
  - United Feature Syndicate (Box 177)
  - United Nations (Box 177)
  - U.S. Senate (Box 177)
  - Urquhart, Fred (Box 177)
  - Val Baker, Denys (Box 177)
  - Valentine, Joseph (Box 177)
  - Vanguard Press Catalogs (Box 177)
  - Vantage Press (Box 177)
  - Varley, Dimitry (Box 177)
  - Venezis, Ilias (Box 177)
  - Venturi, Marcello (Box 177)
  - Verlag, Carl Hanser (Box 177)
  - Vermeer, Ann (Box 177)
  - Vest, Arley (Box 177)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 177)
  - View Inc. (Box 177)
  - Vocational Guidance (Box 177)
  - Wagman, Ben (Box 178)
  - Walker, Nedda (Box 178)
  - Walsh, Mary R. (Box 178)
  - Walton, Stephen (Box 178)
  - Warner, Hank (Box 178)
  - Watkins, John (Box 178)
  - Watkins, Ronny (Box 178)
  - Watson, Elmo S. (Box 178)
  - Watts, Alan (Box 178)
  - Weart, Edith (Box 179)
  - Weaver, Harriett (Box 179)
  - Weidenfeld & Nicolson Ltd. (Box 179)
  - Weiner, Joyce (Box 179)
  - Welch, Jos N. (Box 179)
  - Weng, Wan-Go H.C. (Box 179)
  - Wesley, Charles (Box 179)
  - Western Printing & Lithographing Co. (Box 179)
  - Westheimer, Patricia H. (Box 179)
  - Weybright & Talley Inc. (Box 179)
  - White, William S. (Box 180)
  - Widney, Bette (Box 180)
  - Wier, Ester (Box 180)
  - Wiggins, Marianne (Box 180)
  - Wile, Ira (Box 180)
  - William Morris Agency (Box 180)
  - William Morrow & Co. (Box 180)
  - William Taylor Co. (Box 180)
  - Williams-Heller, Annie & McCarthy, Josephine (Box 180)
  - Williams & Searle (Box 180)
  - Willingham, Calder (Box 181-184)
  - Willingham, Calder (Box 185)
  - Willis, Irene (Box 185)
  - Willumsen, Dorrit (Box 185)
  - Wilson, John (Box 185)
  - Wilson, Joseph (Box 185)
  - Wilson, Morrow (Box 185)
  - Wingate, Allan (Box 186)
  - Winkler, John K. (Box 186)
  - Winnick, Maren B. (Box 186)
  - Winsten, Stephen (Box 186)
  - Wiseman, Ann Sayre (Box 186)
  - Witte, Hazel (Box 186)
  - Wittfogel, Karl A. (Box 186)
  - Wolf, George (Box 187)
  - Wolf, Patricia (Box 187)
  - Wolff, H. (Box 187)
  - Wolff, H. (Box 188)
  - Wolfson, P.J. (Box 188)
  - Wolfson, P.J. (Box 189)
  - Woll, Tommy (Box 189)
  - Wood, Charles Erskine Scott (Box 189)
  - Wood, James (Box 189)
  - Woodward, Hildegard (Box 189)
  - Work, John, M. (Box 189)
  - World Publishing Co. (Box 189)
  - Worsley, Dale (Box 189)
  - Woychek, Dennis (Box 190)
  - Woytinsky, W. S (Box 190)
  - Wright, Helena (Box 191)
  - Writers House Inc (Box 191)
  - Writers Service (Box 191)
  - Yalen-mor (Box 192)
  - Yanoovsky, V.S. (Box 192)
  - Yasuhara, Motosuke (Box 192)
  - Yellowley (Box 192)
  - Young, Art (Box 192)
  - Young, Rosamund (Box 192)
  - Zaidenberg, Arthur (Box 192)
  - Zapper, George (Box 192)
  - Zaturenska, Marya (Box 192)
  - Zlot, William (Box 192)
  - Zola, Emile (Box 192)
  - Zuckmayer, Carl (Box 192)
  - Zumwalt, Eva (Box 192)
- Series VII: Photographs
  - Abercrombie, P.B. (Box 193)
  - Adams, Frank (Box 193)
  - Aistrop, Jack (Box 193)
  - Algren, Nelson (Box 193)
  - Allen, Robert S. (Box 193)
  - Alsop, Gulielma (Box 193)
  - Andrieux, Raymond (Box 193)
  - Arthaud, Claude & Herbert-Stevens, Francis (Box 193)
  - Atwood, Wallace (Box 193)
  - Bacon, Walter (Box 193)
  - Baker, Denys Val (Box 193)
  - Baker, Jacob (Box 193)
  - Baker, Nina B. (Box 193)
  - Barkley, Jane R. (Box 193)
  - Barrett, James W. (Box 193)
  - Beaton-Jones, Cynon (Box 193)
  - Bent, Silas (Box 193)
  - Blackwell, Louise (Box 193)
  - Bolster, Evelyn (Box 193)
  - Bombard, Alain (Box 193)
  - Boulle, Pierre (Box 193)
  - Bowman, W.E. (Box 193)
  - Brandon, Evan (Box 193)
  - Brooke, Jocelyn (Box 193)
  - Bryant, Matt (Box 193)
  - Burnett & Foley (Box 194)
  - Burnett, Constance B. (Box 194)
  - Burress, John (Box 194)
  - Castellanos, Rosario (Box 194)
  - Chaplin, Charles (Box 194)
  - Clarke, Donald H. (Box 194)
  - Clephen-Palmer E. (Box 194)
  - Close, Robert E. (Box 194)
  - Cotten, Lee (Box 194)
  - Dennis, Patrick SEE: Tanner, Patrick (Box 194)
  - DeVries, Robert (Box 194)
  - Donovan, Leo (Box 194)
  - Emery, Anne (Box 194)
  - Farrell, James T. (Box 194)
  - Fisher, Vardis (Box 194)
  - Fleischman, Theo (Box 194)
  - Flornoy, Bertrand (Box 194)
  - Frank, Jane (Box 194)
  - Fuchs, Daniel (Box 195)
  - Funt, Allen (Box 195)
  - Gardner, Leonard SEE: Various (Box 195)
  - Gee, John & Selby, Elliot (Box 195)
  - Geisel, Theodor Seuss (Box 195)
  - Gibbs, Peter (Box 195)
  - Gillett, Margaret & Kehoe, Monika (Box 195)
  - Gillon, Philip (Box 195)
  - Goldberg, Rube & Boal, Sam (Box 195)
  - Golding, Louis (Box 195)
  - Gollomb, Joseph (Box 195)
  - Goodman, Paul (Box 195)
  - Goodrich, Warren (Box 195)
  - Gordon, General (Box 195)
  - Groth, John (Box 195)
  - Haldane, Charlotte (Box 195)
  - Hart, Marion Rice (Box 195)
  - Hearne, John (Box 195)
  - Heimler, Eugene (Box 195)
  - Held, John Jr. (Box 195)
  - Heyen, William (Box 195)
  - Hooten, Barbara & Bill (Box 195)
  - Howard, Joseph (Box 195)
  - Hunter, Edward (Box 195)
  - Huxley (Box 196)
  - Jordan, Philip (Box 196)